export const multipleChoiceQuestions = [
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `2^3`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `8`,
            distractor1: `6`,
            distractor2: `9`,
            distractor3: `16`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `3^3`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `27`,
            distractor1: `9`,
            distractor2: `18`,
            distractor3: `6`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `3^1`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `3`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
            distractor2: `0`,
            distractor3: `1`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `4^3`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `64`,
            distractor1: `12`,
            distractor2: `16`,
            distractor3: `8`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `2^4`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `16`,
            distractor1: `8`,
            distractor2: `4`,
            distractor3: `32`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `5^2`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `25`,
            distractor1: `10`,
            distractor2: `15`,
            distractor3: `20`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `6^2`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `36`,
            distractor1: `12`,
            distractor2: `18`,
            distractor3: `56`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `4^2`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `16`,
            distractor1: `8`,
            distractor2: `12`,
            distractor3: `24`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `1^2`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `1`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{2}`,
            distractor2: `0`,
            distractor3: `2`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\frac{1}{4^2}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{16}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{8}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{4}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{2}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\frac{1}{3^2}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{9}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{6}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{2}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\frac{1}{2^3}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{8}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{4}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{6}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{16}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `3^{-1}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
            distractor1: `-3`,
            distractor2: `=\\frac{1}{3}`,
            distractor3: `3`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `4^{-2}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{16}`,
            distractor1: `-16`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{8}`,
            distractor3: `-8`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\frac{1}{8^2}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{64}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{16}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{32}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{8}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\frac{5}{9^2}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{5}{81}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{5}{18}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{5}{27}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{2}{45}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\frac{3}{7^2}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{3}{49}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{3}{14}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{3}{21}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{3}{28}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `6^{-2}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{6^2}`,
            distractor1: `-6^2`,
            distractor2: `-\\frac{1}{6^2}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{2}{6}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `2^{-3}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{2^3}`,
            distractor1: `-\\frac{1}{2^3}`,
            distractor2: `-2^3`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{2}{3}`,
        }
    },        
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt{4}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `2`,
            distractor1: `16`,
            distractor2: `4`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{2}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt{9}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `3`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{9}`,
            distractor3: `27`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt{16}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `4`,
            distractor1: `2`,
            distractor2: `8`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{4}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt[3]{8}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `2`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{3}{8}`,
            distractor2: `4`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{2}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt[4]{16}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `2`,
            distractor1: `4`,
            distractor2: `8`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{4}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt{36}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `6`,
            distractor1: `3`,
            distractor2: `9`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{6}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt{49}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `7`,
            distractor1: `4`,
            distractor2: `9`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{9}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\sqrt[3]{64}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `4`,
            distractor1: `8`,
            distractor2: `16`,
            distractor3: `2`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `5^{\\frac{1}{2}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\sqrt{5}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{25}`,
            distractor2: `\\sqrt{25}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{5}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `8^{\\frac{1}{3}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\sqrt[3]{8}`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{8}`,
            distractor2: `\\sqrt{8}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `4^{-\\frac{1}{2}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{4}}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt{4}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{4}`,
            distractor3: `-\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{4}}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `8^{-\\frac{1}{3}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{\\sqrt[3]{8}}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt[3]{8}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{8}`,
            distractor3: `-\\frac{1}{\\sqrt[3]{8}}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `16^{-\\frac{1}{4}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{2}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt{16}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{4}`,
            distractor3: `-\\frac{1}{2}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `25^{-\\frac{1}{2}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{25}}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt{25}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{25}`,
            distractor3: `-\\frac{1}{\\sqrt{25}}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `36^{-\\frac{1}{2}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{6}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt{36}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{36}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{8}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `49^{-\\frac{1}{2}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{7}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt{49}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{49}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{9}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `64^{-\\frac{1}{3}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{4}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt[3]{64}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{64}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{16}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `81^{-\\frac{1}{2}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{9}`,
            distractor1: `-\\sqrt{81}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{81}`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `1^{-\\frac{1}{3}}`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `1`,
            distractor1: `-1`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
            distractor3: `-\\frac{1}{3}`,
        }
    },                                
];

export const multipleChoiceQuestionsIntegration = [
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2+C`,
            distractor1: `1`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{2}x+C`,
            distractor3: `x^2+C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad x^2 \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3+C`,
            distractor1: `2x+C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2+C`,
            distractor3: `x^3+C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad x^3 \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{4}x^4+C`,
            distractor1: `3x+C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3+C`,
            distractor3: `x^4+C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad x^n \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{n+1}x^{n+1}+C`,
            distractor1: `nx+C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{n}x^n+C`,
            distractor3: `x^{n+1}+C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 1 \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `x+C`,
            distractor1: `0`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2+C`,
            distractor3: `x^2+C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 3 \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `3x+C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{3}`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3+C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{3}{2}x^2+C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 1,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 3x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{3}{2}x^2+C`,
            distractor1: `2x^3+C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^2+C`,
            distractor3: `3+C`,
        }
    },                
]

export const multipleChoiceQuestionsIntegration2 = [
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x + 1) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2 + x + C`,
            distractor1: `2 + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{2}x + x + C`,
            distractor3: `x^2 + x + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x + 5) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2 + 5x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2 + 5 + C`,
            distractor2: `5x + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2 + x + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (3x + 2) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{3}{2}x^2 + 2x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 2x + C`,
            distractor2: `3x + 2 + C`,
            distractor3: `x^2 + 2x + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x^2 + 1) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2 + x + C`,
            distractor2: `x^2 + 1 + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{4}x^4 + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x^3 + 3) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{4}x^4 + 3x + C`,
            distractor1: `3x + 4 + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 3 + C`,
            distractor3: `x^4 + 3x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x^3 + 2x) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{4}x^4 + x^2 + C`,
            distractor1: `3x + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 2x + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{3}{2}x^2 + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 2,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (3x^2 + 4x) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `x^3 + 2x^2 + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 2x + C`,
            distractor2: `x^3 + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{3}{2}x^2 + C`,
        }
    },                
]

export const multipleChoiceQuestionsIntegration3 = [
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (3x^2 + 2x + 3) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `x^3 + x^2 + 3x + C`,
            distractor1: `3x + 2 + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + \\frac{1}{2}x^2 + 3x + C`,
            distractor3: `x^2 + x + 3+ C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x^2 + 5x + 1) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + \\frac{5}{2}x^2 + x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2 + 5 + C`,
            distractor2: `2x + 5 + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 5x^2 + x + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (2x^2 + 2x + 7) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{2}{3}x^3 + x^2 + 7x + C`,
            distractor1: `x^3 + x^2 + 7 + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 2x + C`,
            distractor3: `x^2 + 2x + 7 + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x^2 + 2x + 1) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + x^2 + x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{2}x^2 + x + C`,
            distractor2: `x^2 + 1 + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{4}x^4 + x^2 + x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (x^3 + 3) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\frac{1}{4}x^4 + 3x + C`,
            distractor1: `3x + 4 + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 3 + C`,
            distractor3: `x^4 + 3x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 3,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad (3x^2 + 2x) \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `x^3 + x^2 + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{3}x^3 + 2x + C`,
            distractor2: `x^3 + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{3}{2}x^2 + C`,
        }
    },                
]

export const multipleChoiceQuestionsIntegration4 = [
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\cos x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\sin x + C`,
            distractor1: `-\\sin x + C`,
            distractor2: `\\sec x + C`,
            distractor3: `\\csc + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\cos x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-\\sin x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\sin + C`,
            distractor2: `\\csc x + C`,
            distractor3: `-\\sec + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -\\sin x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\cos x + C`,
            distractor1: `-\\cos x + C`,
            distractor2: `\\sec x + C`,
            distractor3: `\\csc + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -\\cos x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-\\sin x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\cos x + C`,
            distractor2: `\\sec x + C`,
            distractor3: `\\csc + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\sec^2 x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\tan x + C`,
            distractor1: `\\sec x + C`,
            distractor2: `x + C`,
            distractor3: `\\sin x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 2\\sin x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-2\\cos x + C`,
            distractor1: `2\\cos x + C`,
            distractor2: `\\cos (2x)`,
            distractor3: `-\\cos (2x) + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 3\\cos x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `3\\sin x + C`,
            distractor1: `3\\cos x + C`,
            distractor2: `-3\\cos x`,
            distractor3: `-3\\sin x + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 4,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -3\\sin x \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `3\\cos x + C`,
            distractor1: `-3\\cos x + C`,
            distractor2: `-3\\sin x + C`,
            distractor3: `-3\\sec + C`,
        }
    },                
]

export const multipleChoiceQuestionsIntegration5 = [
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 4e^{2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `2e^{2x} + 4 + C`,
            distractor2: `4e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{2}e^{2x} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 2xe^{x^2} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `e^{x^2} + C`,
            distractor1: `x^2e^{x^2} + C`,
            distractor2: `e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor3: `2e^{x^2} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 3x^2e^{x^3} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `e^{x^3} + C`,
            distractor1: `e^{3x^2} + C`,
            distractor2: `6xe^{3x^2} + C`,
            distractor3: `3e^{x^2} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 3e^{3x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `e^{3x} + C`,
            distractor1: `3e^{3x} + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3} e^{3x} + C`,
            distractor3: `-\\sin x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -2e^{2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `-\\frac{1}{2}e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor2: `-2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor3: `e^{-2x} + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -4e^{2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor2: `-2e^2`,
            distractor3: `-2e^{-2x} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -2e^{-2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{4}e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor2: `-2e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor3: `-e^{-2x} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 5,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad 3e^{-3x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-e^{-3x} + C`,
            distractor1: `-3e^{-3x} + C`,
            distractor2: `e^{-3x} + C`,
            distractor3: `3e^{-3x} + C`,
        }
    },                
]

export const multipleChoiceQuestionsIntegration6 = [
    {
        level: 6,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\frac{1}{x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\ln |x| + C`,
            distractor1: `x \\ln |x| + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{2} x^2 + C`,
            distractor3: `e^{x} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 6,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\frac{1}{x^3} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-\\frac{1}{2} x^{-2} + C`,
            distractor1: `-\\frac{1}{3} x^{-3} + C`,
            distractor2: `\\ln |x^3| + C`,
            distractor3: `\\ln |3x^2| + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 6,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\frac{7}{x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `7 \\ln |x| + C`,
            distractor1: `\\ln |7x| + C`,
            distractor2: `7x + C`,
            distractor3: `7e^x + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 6,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -\\frac{1}{x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `- \\ln |x| + C`,
            distractor1: `- \\frac{1}{2} \ln |x| + C`,
            distractor2: `-\\frac{1}{x} + C`,
            distractor3: `-x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 6,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -e^{-x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `e^{-x} + C`,
            distractor1: `-e^x + C`,
            distractor2: `-e^{-x} + C`,
            distractor3: `e^x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 6,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -4e^{2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor2: `-2e^2`,
            distractor3: `-2e^{-2x} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 6,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -2e^{-2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{4}e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor2: `-2e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor3: `-e^{-2x} + C`,
        }
    },
]

export const multipleChoiceQuestionsIntegration7 = [
    {
        level: 7,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\frac{1}{x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\ln |x| + C`,
            distractor1: `x \\ln |x| + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{2} x^2 + C`,
            distractor3: `e^{x} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 7,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\frac{3x^2}{x^3 + 2} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\ln |x^3 + 2| + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{2} x^2 + C`,
            distractor2: `\\frac{1}{3} x^{-2} + C`,
            distractor3: `\\frac{1}{3} \ln |x^3| + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 7,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\frac{4}{4x + 7} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\ln |4x + 7| + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{4} \ln |4x + 7| + C`,
            distractor2: `x + \\frac{7}{4} + C`,
            distractor3: `7 \\ln |x| + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 7,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -\\frac{3}{3x + 2} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `- \\ln |3x + 2| + C`,
            distractor1: `-\\frac{3}{2} \\ln |3x + 2| + C`,
            distractor2: `-\\frac{1}{3} \\ln |3x + 2| + C`,
            distractor3: `-x + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 7,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad \\frac{2x + 1}{x^2 + x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `\\ln |x^2 + x| + C`,
            distractor1: `-\\ln |x^2 + x| + C`,
            distractor2: `\\ln |2x + 1| + C`,
            distractor3: `\\ln |x^2 + 1| + C`,
        }
    },    
    {
        level: 7,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -4e^{2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `-2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `2e^{2x} + C`,
            distractor2: `-2e^2`,
            distractor3: `-2e^{-2x} + C`,
        }
    },
    {
        level: 7,
        question: `\\int_\\quad^\\quad -2e^{-2x} \\quad dx =`,
        answers: {
            correctAnswer: `e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor1: `\\frac{1}{4}e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor2: `-2e^{-2x} + C`,
            distractor3: `-e^{-2x} + C`,
        }
    },
]
    
export function shuffleArray(array) {
    for(let i = array.length -1; i > 0; i--) {
        const j = Math.floor(Math.random() * (i - 1));
        [array[i], array[j]] = [array[j], array[i]];
    }
    return array;
}